https://www.nugs.net/privacy-policy.html

250,000+ Jams | 25,000+ Shows | 30,000+ Hours of Live Music!
Shop
Hi,
-updated as of April 9, 2019
Thank you for visiting nugs.net. Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy describes the information we collect, what we do with it, and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at nugs.net. Please review our privacy policy as it may change in the future (when we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy) and contact us at  privacy@nugs.net if you have any questions or concerns.
The Information We Collect
At nugs.net and nugs.net websites, you can order products, express an opinion, and subscribe to services such as online newsletters and paid streaming. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, location, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, contact preferences, credit card information, Internet protocol address, date of birth, and details of how you use and interact with our websites (e.g. your search queries, a record of customer service emails).
At certain parts of some of our websites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g. Safari, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using and information about your Internet service provider (e.g. Comcast, AT&T) or device (e.g. iPhone X, MacBook Pro) and other user-related general data (e.g. zip code, area code).
How We Use the Information
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when a concert you have purchased is available for download, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us. If you enter into a giveaway, contest or other promotion, we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.
The information we collect in connection with our website is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you new products, programs, or services. As is the case with most Internet services, we obtain some information automatically and store it in log files. We use this and other information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, to improve our products and services, and to gather generalized demographic information about our users. We may use this information to market and advertise our products and services.
You are not required to provide any personally identifiable information that we have requested, but if you choose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our products or services or respond to any questions you may have.
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may share non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners and use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.
We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process (e.g. in response to a court order or a subpoena) or to enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations. We also may disclose such information to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, intellectual property violations, security or technical issues, to protect our operations or users, or to respond to a law enforcement agency's request. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger or sale we may transfer any and all information we collect to the relevant third party.
Agents and contractors of nugs.net who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for nugs.net.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.
Finally, nugs.net websites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses. For example, if you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out by updating your settings or contacting us at  privacy@nugs.net.
Cookies
To enhance your experience with our website, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at nugs.net.com (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our website.
You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associates with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.
Our Commitment to Security
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.
California Privacy Disclosures:
We do not track our customers across third party websites, however some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they provide you content, which allows them to determine what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, your browser should allow you to set the Do Not Track (DNT) signal so that third parties know you do not want to be tracked. Third parties that have content embedded on nugs.net websites may set cookies on a user’s browser and/or collect information about the fact that a web browser visited a specific nugs.net website from a certain IP address. Third parties cannot obtain any other personally identifiable information from nugs.net’s websites unless you provide it to them directly. Information collected by third parties is governed by their privacy practices.
Nugs.net offers interactive services which allow you to post content to share publicly or with friends.  At any time you can contact privacy@nugs.net to delete or remove content you have posted using the deletion or removal options within our service.  Although we offer deletion capability for our services, please be aware that the removal of content may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of that content or information posted through the services.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about the nugs.net Privacy Policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at privacy@nugs.net or at the address below:
Nugs.net Enterprises, Inc. 1383 Ninth Avenue, San Francisco, CA 94122 attn: Privacy
